Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide.
Raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are?
He destroyed the fin!
He's trying to sink my ship.
You dare defy me?
Dean, blow his head off right now!
What are you waiting for?
But he...
he saved our lives when we were starving.
He gave us food.
Okay, I don't see why you're all so upset.
I Didn't sink it
Back off sure boy.
It's not your fight, but I
will what I'm going to sink it
You bastard, that's what you're doing.
You can't sink this shit,
but if the restaurant's gone There's
no reason to attack then, is there?
No!
This ship saved my life.
I owe everything to her, and
you will not take that away!
You're gonna die for
a dumb old restaurant?
Are you stupid?
What'd you say?
Getting killed?
That's how you want to repay your debt?
The old man didn't save you so
that you could kill yourself.
He did it so you could do
something with your life.
Not to die like a fool!
And so your big idea is
to help them attack us?
Boys, there's no need
for friends to fight,
especially when there's
nothing either of you can do.
Not while there's a big shotgun
pressed right up against
the old man's chef's hat.
Your problem began when you decided
to come up against the Krieg pirates.
Fire, Pearl!
Now you will burn!
Ginny!
What did you do?
Ginny?
I'm sorry, Pearl.
You're in my way.
Ginny!
You have betrayed your
captain and your ship!
I'm sorry, Dunkrie.
But he saved our lives.
I can't kill him.
Not like this.
He deserves better.
He deserves to face death standing up.
But I promise you, he'll
still die by my hand.
Oh, great.
My chief commander has now
completely lost his marbles.
He's their chief commander?
I guess.
Did you see him crush that guy, though?
One blow and his shield was in pieces.
Now that's power.
My plan worked perfectly.
And now he's out in the open.
You liar.
There's no way you thought
that this would happen.
Sanji.
Look, I don't want to ruin this ship,
but I think it's too late for that.
You're going to get to this
restaurant without killing me?
You got another thing coming.
Sounds fair.
And it will be an absolute
pleasure to kill you.
My good friend.
Gee, that's comforting.
Asshole.
You as well, chore boy.
Gee, thanks, but I'm not
afraid of any Krieg pirate.
Little dwarf!
I'm right here ready to die, little man.
I'm gonna stuff that stupid
Straw Hat right down your throat.
We're the three pirates,
rulers of the East Blue.
Hmm, only because you outnumbered
the other pirates in the East Blue.
Oh boy, now you really pissed
him off. Guess I was right.
You're dead meat!
Let's get him!
Hold your place!
But Don Krieg, he can't say that!
You only prove his point when you lose
control or whine like little babies.
You see me trembling with anger?
Only the weak react to mere words.
Donkreek pirates run from no man!
Yes, sir!
Gain, it's your job to
take care of that cook.
I'll handle the little boy.
That brat is all mine.
I understand.
Yes, Donkreek.
Hey, boy,
you can try your devil
fruit magic against me,
but I've seen it all before and have
never been defeated by such trickery.
When you experience the full force
that conquered the entire East Blue,
then you'll understand the
meaning of power, chore boy.
Your voice is getting on my nerves.
I'm gonna kick your ass.
It's as simple as that.
Hold on just a second.
I'll be right there.
The impudence.
That cook is done for now. Yeah, man.
When Ginny takes out his weapons,
he's through-screwing around.
Just look at him.
They call him a cold-hearted demon.
He's our cool-headed, cold-hearted
Pirate Fleet Chief Commander, Ginny.
It doesn't matter if you beg for mercy,
he'll still laugh in your
face while he kills you.
I'm sorry, Sanji, but I can't be defeated.
Yeah, go ahead.
Tell yourself that.
Here I come!
Ah!
Oh, yeah! You Sodom!
Ah-ha!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
And now, it's time for
you to accept defeat.
Die!
That cook kicked Kaido in the head.
Yeah, I couldn't believe it.
Do you think he's still alive?
Enough!
Stop!
After all this time, you should know a
hell of a lot better than that, you idiots.
There's a reason I trust him
above any of my other pirate crew.
Ginny is always a cool-headed,
cold-hearted demon, and he never quits!
I can't believe Sanji is getting up.
He should lie back down.
After what he's been through, his
ribs must be completely smashed.
Well, that wasn't too
bad, Chief Commander.
Let me know when you're
ready to really fight.
He's just sitting there.
Now it's ass-kicking time.
Don't hurt yourself.
You're a bastard!
Don't you want to fight me?
Fight you?
Do I really have to?
If all I want to do is kill
you, that's enough for me.
Really don't have any patience
for your stupid games little fool.
Oh, yeah How about I butt your head off?
Sanchi!
Woo-hoo!
Pulverize the rest of them!
Yeah, what he said! Crap!
If only he hadn't fought
that pearl guy first!
Yeah, I don't think you'll survive
another hit from those balls.
Go ahead.
You hit like a girl anyway.
He's too strong for me.
Now die.
Bye, Sanji.
What was that? Your pity?
I'm not dead yet!
Chief Commander!
Oh no!
No!
He can't take it!
He's gonna kill himself
just trying to fight!
Damn bastard.
I can't, Dahlkrieg!
I won't do it!
I can't!
I'm sorry, Captain.
What did you say?
I won't do what you want.
Take it and leave me alone.
I'm sorry.
Thank you so much.
I thought it was over.
I truly thought I was going to die.
This food, it's delicious.
I've never eaten food this could before.
Of course it is.
Sorry.
You'll probably get yelled at or fired
because you gave me that food for free.
Now there's not proof, so there's
no way for me to get yelled at.
He treated me with such respect
and decency and kindness.
That's why I can't bring
myself to kill him.
Don't get caught again.
I've always been loyal to you.
Up till now, I've believed
in what we've done.
I respect you and appreciate
all you have given me.
Trusting me as your chief
commander was the honor of my life.
Until this moment,
I have obeyed every single order you have
given me without ever questioning it.
I can't live with myself if I kill
this man, and I cannot break my oath.
Please, I beg you, let me
disobey just this one order.
Please, Don Krieg.
Listen, can't we just leave?
They can keep the
restaurant for themselves.
You little son of a bitch!
You think you can defy my orders
and then tell me what to do?
It's pathetic.
Morality, sympathy, weaknesses I
never expected to see from you.
You are not my chief commander anymore!
Pirates step aside.
No, not the gas.
He's going to use the MH5.
We're all gonna die.
What? Who's in gas?
Where's my mask?
Masks on. Move it. Move it.
He's using MH5.
Gas is a coward's weapon.
You bastard.
You'll kill us all.
The only thing that matters in a battle
is who ends up winning, even
if more have got to die.
Poison gas is just a means to
an end.
Victory is all that decides
what's right and what's wrong.
If you are dead,
nobody's gonna hear you complain anyway.
When you don't hesitate to do
unspeakable, horrible things,
that is true power.
He's insane.
Might as well throw that gas mask away!
You're no longer worthy
to be a Karoo pirate.
Die!
I'm not going to let
that happen, you bastard!
You're wasting your time!
Tribute!
Crap!
Keen!
You don't have to listen to that blowhard,
because I'm going to kick his ass!
No!
My captain cannot be defeated!
Don Krieg is the strongest man
alive, and I respect his punishment.
Will you please snap out of it?
He is going to kill you!
I deserve it.
Obeying my emotions meant
betraying my captain.
If I were in his position, then
I would have done the same thing.
And now, death is the
only honor I have left.
George!
Why?
Heh, so you've remembered your place.
But it's much too late for that.
Now you will both die together.
It's the MH5!
Poison, gas bomb, fire!
Get inside the restaurant!
Thank you!
Sanji King! Catch!
Now for mine!
Where'd they go?
This is power!
I'm alive!
That mask appeared just in time!
What a crazy bastard.
He tried to kill us all.
That guy's gotta be insane.
I can't believe he used poison gas.
He must be a demon.
No human would do that.
Do you think Sanji and Shura
Boy made it? I don't know.
Look, the poison gas is clearing up.
Ginny!
Let go!
You can let go now!
Hey Ginny, are you okay?
It's your mask you gave it to me.
What a fool you are paying for a
plate of food with your life oh!
Well maybe you'll learn when you're dead.
Ginny.
So, it seems...
Don Krieg was not the right
man for you to follow, was he?
It figures that you still feel for
that pathetic scum. Scum? That's right!
Anyone who loses focus and betrays
my ship is worthless to me.
They'll almost certainly do it again.
Putting him out of his misery
is an act of mercy to keep him
from dishonoring himself in the
future and endangering my crew.
But he just...
I never thought the captain
would kill his chief commander.
I know.
Ginny has been his right-hand man for even
longer than I've been part of the crew.
That's right.
See, no one's ever showed more loyalty to
Don Krieg than Ginny has over the years.
How could he forget what Ginny
did for us after we escaped
from the Grand Line and
full-body's marines were after us?
It was a miracle we escaped.
Yeah, he was willing to sacrifice
his life for us by acting as a decoy.
Without him, we wouldn't
have made it out of there.
Gein's laid down his life for
Don Krieg a hundred times easy.
I can't believe the captain would
kill him with such little care.
That's so cruel.
Patty, get the kit, hurry!
It's for food poisoning.
I don't think it'll work on gas, Sanji.
I don't care.
We have to try.
Put the mask on him.
It will detoxify the gas in his lungs.
Then bring him upstairs
and let him breathe.
It's the only chance we have to save him.
Patty, Carney, hurry. Help me.
All right already. Me too.
All right, I'm coming.
It's no use.
He's going to die within the hour.
Don't you dare die, Ginny!
You can't let someone like him win!
Stick around, now I'm mad!
You'll want to see what I'm
going to do to him next!
You can't defeat him!
Wait a second, attacking him
head on is exactly what he wants!
He's strongest that way!
I'm not worried!
Go ahead and give it your best shot!
Dumb kid!
When you lose your patience,
you become easy prey!
You are only running toward
one thing, chore boy!
And that is!
He's dead, really dead!
Your funeral!
My funeral?
Oh, no!
Get out of there!
He got hit.
He's done!
Poor guy.
Here we go!
Just try it!
He's got no place to hit!
Castle!
No!
Don Krieg is down!
That punk got him!
What is that kid, anyway?
He punched him right through the spanks!
That's messed up.
I've never seen him get hit
in any kind of fight, ever.
He busted right through that porcupine
cape and smashed him right in the face.
I, I can't believe it.
So is this my funeral?
Yours!
You can't kill me.
Little spikes.
My funeral.
Will take more than this!
You'll have to do better than that?
if you want to beat me.
Because I don't think it's
time for me to die just yet.
I know one thing. He's nuts.
I've seen one or two like him before.
Stubborn kids who'd rather die than have
to turn away from a
fight once it's started.
He'll stay that's for sure.
I'm glad he's with us because
guys like that are hell to fight.
I don't care if he wins or loses.
I consider it an honor just to be able?
I'll be able to watch him.
Was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
My only dream.
I won't stop chasing it.
Until it comes true.
But if the world ever changes!
I call out your name.
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?